Guide to the Rice University Will Rice College Records, 1957-2017 UA 073
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series XII: Governance, 1961-2013; 228981
  - Treasurer's Papers - David Greene, 1990/1991; 228991 (Box 23, Folder 1)
  - Vice President's Papers - Jessica Brady, 1991/1992; 228990 (Box 23, Folder 2)
  - Vice President's Papers - Cameron McKelvey, 1992/1993; 228989 (Box 23, Folder 3)
  - Vice President's Papers - Jay Chance, 1993/1994; 228988 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - Vice President's Papers - Deborah Lutes, 1994/1995; 228987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Vice President's Papers - Adam Lasics, 1995/1996; 228986 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Vice President's Papers - Brooke Cooper, 1996/1997; 228985 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Vice President's Papers - Dennis Geels, 1997/1998; 228984 (Box 23, Folder 8)
  - Vice President's Papers - Cindy Choi, 1998/1999; 228983 (Box 23, Folder 9)
  - Vice President's Papers - Liz Jackson, 1999/2000; 228982 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Series XIII: Masters, RA, College Coordinators, and Associates, 1957-2013; 228964
  - Associates Correspondence and Lists, 1991-2000; 228980 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Associates Event Invitations, 1980-1989; 228979 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Associates Event Invitations, 1990-1999; 228978 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Associates Event Invitations, 2000-2009; 228977 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Associates Event Invitations, 2010-; 228976 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Associates Event Invitations, n.d.; 228975 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Associates Meet-Sheet Questionnaire, n.d.; 228974 (Box 23, Folder 17)
  - Associates Event Invitation, November 1994; 228973 (Box 23, Folder 18)
  - Barbara Willis Private Dining Room, 2001; 228972 (Box 23, Folder 19)
  - "Little Bobby" Duncan Art, 1998; 228971 (Box 23, Folder 20)
  - Masters List, 1957-2013; 228970 (Box 23, Folder 21)
  - Masters, RA, and College Coordinator Search, 1996-2000; 228969 (Box 23, Folder 22)
  - Masters Search, 2001; 228968 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - New Associates Letter, c. 2010; 228967 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Outstanding and Distinguished Associates, 1995-2012; 228966 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Resident Associates, 1982-1989; 228965 (Box 24, Folder 4)
- Series XIV: Minutes, 1984-2003; 228950
  - 1984/1985, 228963 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - 1990/1991, 228962 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - 1991/1992, 228961 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - 1993/1994, 228960 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - 1994/1995, 228959 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - 1995/1996, 228958 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - 1996/1997, 228957 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - 1997/1998, 228956 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - 1998/1999, 228955 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - 1999/2000, 228954 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - 2000/2001, 228953 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - 2001/2002, 228952 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - 2002/2003, 228951 (Box 24, Folder 17)
- Series XV: O-Week, 1966-2012; 228923
  - Freshman Week Letters, 1966-1967; 228949 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - O-Week Documents, 1996; 228948 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Han Solo-Week Book, 1996; 228947 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - O-Week Documents, 1997; 228946 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - O-Week Documents, 1998; 228945 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - O-Week Documents, 1999; 228944 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - O-Week Documents, 2000; 228943 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Play-Doh Week Book, 2000; 228942 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - O-Week Documents, 2001; 228941 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - Where'd They Go? Week Book, 2001; 228940 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - O-Week Documents, 2002; 228939 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - O-Week Documents, 2003; 228938 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - O-Week Documents, 2004; 228937 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - O-Week Documents, 2005; 228936 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - O-Week Documents, 2006; 228935 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - Winnebago Week Book, 2006; 228934 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - O-Week Documents, 2007; 228933 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - Bellagio-Week Book, 2007; 228932 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - O-Week Documents, 2008; 228931 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - Speedo-Week Book, 2008 (Box 25, Folder 15)
  - O-Week Documents, 2009; 228930 (Box 25, Folder 16)
  - Mojo-Week Book, 2009; 228929 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - O-Week Documents, 2010; 228928 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Uh-Oh Week Book, 2010; 228927 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - O-Week Documents, 2011; 228926 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Dojo-Week Book, 2011; 228925 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - O-Week Documents, 2012; 228924 (Box 26, Folder 6)
- Series XVI: Student Life, 1960-2013; 228894
  - Awards Night, 1990; 228922 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Awards Night, 1991; 228921 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Awards Night, 1992; 228920 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Awards Night, 1993; 228919 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Awards Night, 1995; 228918 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Awards Night, 1996; 228917 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Awards Night, 1997; 228916 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Awards Night, 1998; 228915 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Awards Night, 1999; 228914 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Awards Night, 2000; 228913 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Awards Night, 2011; 228912 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - Awards Night, 2012; 228911 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Awards Night, 2013; 228910 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Beer Bike, 1980-1997; 228909 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - College Courses, 1980-2000; 228908 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - College Day Speeches, 1960-1982; 228907 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Commencement, 1999; 228906 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Frisbee Golf, 1990; 228905 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Homecoming, 1983-1990; 228904 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Inaugural Concert, 1990; 228903 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Invitations, 1990-1999; 228902 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Invitations, 2000-; 228901 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Invitations, n.d.; 228900 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - Senior Events, 1984-2002; 228899 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Theater, 1990-2001; 228898 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Will Rice Day, 1990-1995; 228897 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Worden Ranch, 1983-1994; 228896 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - WRC Art Show/Art Festival, 1977-1995; 228895 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - Doc C's 50th Year Celebration, November 8, 2014 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Series XVII: Negatives, Photographs, and Slides, 228852
  - Subseries A: Negatives, 228888
    - Beer Bike, 1998; 228893 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - O-Week, 2000s; 228892 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Student Life, 1990s-2000s; 228891 (Box 27, Folder 12)
    - Theater, 1990s-2000s; 228890 (Box 27, Folder 13)
    - Where'd They Go? Week, 2001; 228889 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - Subseries B: Photographs, 228855
    - As Seen on O-Week, 2002; 228887 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    - Beer Bike, 1996; 228886 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    - Beer Bike, 1998; 228885 (Box 27, Folder 17)
    - Beer Bike, 1999; 228884 (Box 27, Folder 18)
    - Beer Bike, 2000; 228883 (Box 27, Folder 19)
    - Beer Bike, 2001; 228882 (Box 27, Folder 20)
    - Beer Bike, 2002; 228881 (Box 27, Folder 21)
    - Beer Bike, 2003; 228880 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Beer Bike, 2008; 228879 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Beer Bike, 2011; 228878 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Beer Bike, 2012; 228877 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - Beer Bike, 2000s; 228876 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - Dojo-Week, 2001; 228875 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - Graduation, 2003; 228874 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - Graduation, 2000s; 228873 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - New Students, 1998; 228872 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - New Student Cards, 1999; 228871 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - New Student Cards, 2000; 228870 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - New Student Cards, 2001; 228869 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Oh, Behave Week, 1999; 228868 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Play-doh Week (1 of 2), 2000; 228867 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Play-doh Week (2 of 2), 2000; 228866 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Masters, RAs, and Associates, 1970s-2000s; 228865 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - Rizzo-Week, 1998; 228864 (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Student Life, 1990s-2000s; 228863 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Student Life, 2011; 228862 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - Student Life, 2012; 228861 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Theater, 1990s-2000s; 228860 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Uh-Oh Week, 2010; 228859 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Where'd They Go? Week (1 of 2), 2001; 228858 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Where'd They Go? Week (2 of 2), 2001; 228857 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Will Rice Day, 1999; 228856 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Subseries C: Slides, 228853
    - Powderpuff Game, 1990s; 228854 (Box 30, Folder 6)
- Series XVIII: Media, 228824
  - Subseries A: Beta, 228850
    - The Rice Myth, 228851 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Subseries B: CDs, 228846
    - Beer Bike (4 CDs), 2009-2011; 228849 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Belly Dancing Class, 2009; 228848 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - O-Week images, 2008; 228847 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Subseries C: DVDs, 228840
    - Beer Bike (7 DVDs), 1996-1997, 2001-2004; 228845 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Gilbert and Sullivan's Patience, 2005; 228844 (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - Mr. Will Rice (2 DVDs), 2004, 2010; 228843 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - O-Week, 1995; 228842 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Will Rice College: The First 50 Years: A "Doc"-umentary (2 DVDs), 2007; 228841 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Subseries D: Floppy Disk, 228838
    - Student photos, 2000 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - O-Week files, 2001 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Subseries E: Mini DV, 228836
    - Will Rice 50th, 2007; 228837 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Subseries F: VHS, 228830
    - Beer Bike (2 tapes), 1996-1997; 228835 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Beer Bike (2 tapes), 2001-2002; 228834 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Beer Bike (2 tapes), 2003; 228833 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Beer Bike, 2004; 228832 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - O-Week, 1995; 228831 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Subseries G: USB, 228828
    - USB (2), 1998-2013; 228829
      These USBs contain information from some of the other media found in this series, more specifically, subseries B, parts of subseries C, subseries D, and subseries H. It also contains videos uploaded to the Will Rice College YouTube account.
  - Subseries H: Zip Disk, 228825
    - O-Week files (4 disks) (1 of 2), 2000-2002; 228827 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - O-Week files (4 disks) (2 of 2), 2000-2002; 228826 (Box 32, Folder 5)
- Series XIX: Memorabilia, 228816
  - Beer Bike book, 2010; 228823 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Annual Inter-College Chorus Award Plaque, 1958-1967; 228822 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Shot glass with phoenix, n.d.; 228821 (Box 33, Item 1)
  - Beer Bike T-Shirt with Gilbert Cuthbertson's face, 2008; 228820 (Box 33, Item 2)
  - Beer Bike T-Shirt, 2013; 228819 (Box 33, Item 3)
  - 90's 2.O-Week T-Shirt, 2013; 228818 (Box 33, Item 4)
  - Mask with phoenix (Box 33)
  - Black Will Rice Blazer [vault], 1960s; 228817
    Worn primarily by men's chorus members during the 1960s.
    Separated Materials
    Moved to Rice Historic Clothing Collection
  - Beer Bike T-Shirt, 1985, 1988, 1989, 1992, 1995, 1997-2002, 2004, 2012 (Box 34)
  - Beer Bike Sweep T-Shirt, 1986, 1999, 2009 (Box 34)
  - Beer Bike Security, 2006 (Box 34)
  - Graduation stole, n.d. (Box 34)
- Series XX: Digital Archive
  General
  These items were downloaded from the Will Rice College Digital Archive Google Drive, converted to pdf files, saved to an internal server, and printed. The digital files will be kept until June 2017. After that, the digital files will be deleted, but the physical files will remain in the collection.
  - Subseries A: C.W. McCullagh, 2004/2005
    - Agendas (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Alcohol (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - Budget (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Constitution (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Elections (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Emails (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Logos (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - President (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Resident Associates (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - President C.W. McCullagh files
  - Subseries B: Caitlin Weidig, 2005/2006
    - Agendas (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Elections (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Events (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - President (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - President Caitlin Weidig files
  - Subseries C: Brian Schwab, 2006/2007
    - Awards (Box 35, Folder 14)
    - Beer Bike (Box 35, Folder 15)
    - Constitution (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - Court (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Diet (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence (Box 35, Folder 19-20)
    - Endowment (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Fire Alarms (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Masters and RAs (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - President (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Treasurer (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - President Brian Schwab files
  - Subseries D: Roger Sharp, 2007/2008
    - President (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - President Roger Sharp files
  - Subseries E: Rahul Agrawal, 2008/2009
    - Agendas (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - Beer Bike (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - Constitution (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - Housing (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - President Rahul Agrawal files
  - Subseries F: Kyle Clark, 2009/2010
    - Beer Bike (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Budget (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Constitution (Box 36, Folder 1-2)
    - Construction - McMurtry College (Box 36, Folder 3)
    - Diet (Box 36, Folder 4)
    - Key Chain (Box 36, Folder 5)
    - MojO-Week (Box 36, Folder 6)
    - President (Box 36, Folder 7)
    - Socials Committee (Box 36, Folder 8)
    - Transition (Box 36, Folder 9)
    - President Kyle Clark files
  - Subseries G: Nico Feltman, 2010/2011
    - President (Box 36, Folder 10)
    - President Nico Feltman files
  - Subseries H: Eddie Reyes, 2011/2012
    - Alcohol Probation (Box 36, Folder 11)
    - At-Large Reps (Box 37, Folder 1)
    - Diet (Box 37, Folder 2)
    - O-Week (Box 37, Folder 3)
    - President (Box 37, Folder 4)
    - Resident Associates (Box 37, Folder 5)
    - TGIFs (Box 37, Folder 6)
    - President Eddie Reyes files
  - Subseries I: Brynnan Webster, 2012/2013
    - Centennial (Box 37, Folder 7)
    - Diet (Box 37, Folder 8)
    - President (Box 37, Folder 9)
    - President Brynnan Webster files
  - Subseries J: Won Hee Lee, 2013/2014
    - Associates (Box 37, Folder 10)
    - President Won Hee Lee files
  - Subseries K: Meg Cornaghie, 2014/2015
    - Associates (Box 37, Folder 11)
    - Directors (Box 37, Folder 12)
    - O-Week (Box 37, Folder 13)
    - President (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Secretary (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Treasurer (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Vice President (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - President Meg Cornaghie files
  - Subseries L: Derek Brown, 2015/2016
    - President Derek Brown files
- Series XXI: Books and Manuals
  - ESPN 8 "the ocho" Week Book, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Magisters search, 2006 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - O-Week Advisor Training manual, 2007 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - O-Week Advisor training manual, 2009 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - The Phoenix, 1998 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Will Rice Day, 2005 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Yo Ho HO-Week book, 2004 (Box 39, Folder 7)